{
    "id": "27a8e1e984db4edf9b8355e8730d655b",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is Jane ——————– works with my sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ———————— watch had been stolen complained to the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Mary had a little lamb ———————- fleece was as white as snow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ———————- I live is very small.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The castle ———————– stands on the hill is 500 years old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know the man ———————– just walked in?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ———————– laughs last laughs best.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got the books ———————– you were looking for.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know the reason ————————- she hates me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the road ————————- leads to the temple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}